{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Appliance Refinishers \u0026 Painters","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40173/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40173,"taskName":"Appliance - Refinish","taskDescription":"Refinish Appliances","xmTaskDescriptor":"Appliance Refinishers \u0026 Painters","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":7,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Appliance major dryer microwave machine","textMessagingName":"Refin Appliance","rolloverLongDesc":"Through cleaning, chroming \u0026 repair (and the use of instruments such as a sandblaster, kiln \u0026 sprayers), these professionals can make older appliances look new again.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes matching existing appliances \u0026 updating appearance.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Refinish Appliances.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Appliance Refinishing \u0026 Painting \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":27,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Appliance Refinish","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Appliance - Refinish","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Appliance Refinisher","urlName":"Appliance-Refinish","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Appliance Refinishers \u0026 Painters - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e","searchKeywords":"Appliance, oven, refrigerator, dishwasher, microwave, dryer, range, washer, washing machine","emcCategoryOid":-12003,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":483,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40173/":{"taskOID":40173,"originalTaskOID":40173,"setID":483,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4144,"questionDisplayText":"Appliance(s) Needing Paint/Refinish","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which appliance(s) do you need painted/refinished? (Check all that apply.)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5099,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Refrigerator","answerDisplayText":"Refrigerator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5036,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Range/Cooktop","answerDisplayText":"Range/Cooktop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4500,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oven","answerDisplayText":"Oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3420,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Kitchen exhaust fan","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen exhaust fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1953,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dishwasher","answerDisplayText":"Dishwasher","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3837,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Microwave oven","answerDisplayText":"Microwave oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6483,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Trash Compactor","answerDisplayText":"Trash Compactor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1460,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Clothes washer","answerDisplayText":"Clothes washer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1459,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Clothes Dryer","answerDisplayText":"Clothes Dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3809,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Metal cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Metal cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4143,"questionDisplayText":"New Paint or Touch Up","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How do you want the appliance painted?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6442,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Touch up","answerDisplayText":"Touch up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5187,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repaint in same color","answerDisplayText":"Repaint in same color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1336,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Change color to match others","answerDisplayText":"Change color to match others","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4144,"questionDisplayText":"Appliance(s) Needing Paint/Refinish","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Which appliance(s) do you need painted/refinished? (Check all that apply.)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5099,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Refrigerator","answerDisplayText":"Refrigerator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5036,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Range/Cooktop","answerDisplayText":"Range/Cooktop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4500,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oven","answerDisplayText":"Oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3420,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Kitchen exhaust fan","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen exhaust fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1953,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dishwasher","answerDisplayText":"Dishwasher","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3837,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Microwave oven","answerDisplayText":"Microwave oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6483,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Trash Compactor","answerDisplayText":"Trash Compactor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1460,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Clothes washer","answerDisplayText":"Clothes washer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1459,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Clothes Dryer","answerDisplayText":"Clothes Dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3809,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Metal cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Metal cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5099,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Refrigerator","answerDisplayText":"Refrigerator","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5036,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Range/Cooktop","answerDisplayText":"Range/Cooktop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4500,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Oven","answerDisplayText":"Oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3420,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Kitchen exhaust fan","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen exhaust fan","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1953,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Dishwasher","answerDisplayText":"Dishwasher","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3837,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Microwave oven","answerDisplayText":"Microwave oven","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6483,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Trash Compactor","answerDisplayText":"Trash Compactor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1460,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Clothes washer","answerDisplayText":"Clothes washer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1459,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Clothes Dryer","answerDisplayText":"Clothes Dryer","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3809,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Metal cabinets","answerDisplayText":"Metal cabinets","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":4143,"questionDisplayText":"New Paint or Touch Up","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How do you want the appliance painted?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":6442,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Touch up","answerDisplayText":"Touch up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5187,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repaint in same color","answerDisplayText":"Repaint in same color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1336,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Change color to match others","answerDisplayText":"Change color to match others","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":6442,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Touch up","answerDisplayText":"Touch up","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5187,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Repaint in same color","answerDisplayText":"Repaint in same color","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1336,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Change color to match others","answerDisplayText":"Change color to match others","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}